// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "The solar system formed from a cloud of fog is a theory:",
    answer: "Nebula",
    options: ["Big Bang", "Planetesimal", "Twin Star", "Nebula"],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "What is a planet that lies beyond the orbit of the planet Earth called?",
    answer: "Superior",
    options: ["In", "Superior", "Outside", "Inferior"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The inner planet group is?",
    answer: "Mercury, Venus, Earth",
    options: [
      "Mercury, Venus, Earth",
      "Earth, Mars, Jupiter",
      "venus, Earth, Mars",
      "Mars, Jupiter, Saturn",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question:
      "Model of the solar system which states that the earth is the center of the solar system?",
    answer: "Geosentris",
    options: ["Heliosentris", "Koosentris", "Geosentris", "Mediusentris"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Keepler's third law is called law?",
    answer: "Harmonic",
    options: ["Harmonic", "Broad Similarity", "Elipse", "Gravity"],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The planet that is large in size and the element is gas is?",
    answer: "Saturn and Uranus",
    options: ["Jupiter and Mars", "Saturn and Uranus", "Mercury and Venus", "Neptune and Earth"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following planets has the longest revolution time?",
    answer: "Neptune",
    options: ["Mercury", "Venus", "Uranus", "Neptune"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The biggest element of the sun",
    answer: "Hydrogen",
    options: ["Helium", "Oxygen", "Hydrogen", "Carbon Dioxide"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Objects in the solar system that revolve around the planets",
    answer: "Satellite",
    options: ["Comet", "Satellite", "Meteorite", "Asteroids"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The time it takes the sun's rays to reach the earth",
    answer: "8 minutes",
    options: ["7 minutes", "8 minutes", "9 minutes", "10 minutes"],
  }
];
